Soviet Union and Russia Roman Catholic Subject Files, Inclusive: 1930-2003, undated, Bulk: 1971-1988, undated
Baylor University, The Keston Center for Religion, Politics, and Society
- Samizdat, 1964-1988, undated; 3
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers. Fines, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers Trials, 1964, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers. Imprisonments, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers. State Expropriation and Desecration of Church Buildings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Clergy. General, 1978, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Contacts with International Organizations, 1979 May (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for the Defense of Believers' Rights (1 of 5), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for the Defense of Believers' Rights (2 of 5), 1979 January-February (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for the Defense of Believers' Rights (3 of 5), 1979 April-September (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for the Defense of Believers' Rights (4 of 5), 1979 October-December (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Catholic Committee for the Defense of Believers' Rights (5 of 5), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Roman Catholic Church. Samizdat Publications. Regarding the Situation of Lithuanians in Belorussian Republic, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. General, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Gajauskas, Balys, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Petkus, Viktoras, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Individual Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Plumpa, Petras, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania-State Relations, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. General, 1969, 1975, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Trials. General, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Trials. Fr. Antanas Seskevicius, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Believers in Lithuania. Imprisonments. General, 1975, 1977-1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Oppressive Practices against Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. State Interference in Church Affairs. General, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Parish Life, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Hierarchy, 1972, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Defense of Believers' Rights. General, 1974-1975, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Defense of Believers' Rights. Lithuanian Memorandum, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Emigration on Religious Grounds, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Alma Mater, no. 1, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Alma Mater, no. 3, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Alma Mater, no. 4, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA. General, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 2, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 7 (47), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 8 (48), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 9 (49), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 11 (51), 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 12 (52), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 13 (53), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 14 (54), 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 15 (55), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 16 (56) (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 16 (56) (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 17 (57), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 18 (58), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 19 (59), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 20 (60), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 21 (61), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 22 (62), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 23 (63), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 24 (64), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 25 (65), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 27 (67), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 28 (68), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 29 (69), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 30 (70), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 32 (72), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 33 (73), 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 35 (75), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 36 (76), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 37 (77), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 39 (79), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 40 (80), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 41 (81), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 48 (88), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 49 (89), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 50 (90), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA, no. 52 (92), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRA. Notes, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. AUSRELE, no. 1, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church. General (1 of 2), 1972-1976 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church. General (2 of 2), 1976-1977, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 1, 1972 (1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 1, 1972 (2 of 3), 1972, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 1, 1972 (3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 2, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 3, 1972, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 4, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 5, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 6, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 7, 1973, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 8, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 9, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 10, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 11, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 12, 1974 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 12, 1974 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 13, 1974 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 13, 1974 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 14, 1974 (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 14, 1974 (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 15, 1975 (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 15, 1975 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 16, 1975 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 16, 1975 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 17, 1975 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 17, 1975 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 18, 1975 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 18, 1975 (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 19, 1975 (1 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 19, 1975 (2 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 19, 1975 (3 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 20, 1975 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 20, 1975 (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 21, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 21, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 22, 1976 (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 22, 1976 (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 22, 1976 (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 23, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 23, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 24, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 24, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 25, 1976 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 25, 1976 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 26, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 26, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 27, 1977 (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 27, 1977 (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 27, 1977 (3 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 28, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 28, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 29, 1977 (1 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 29, 1977 (2 of 3) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 29, 1977 (3 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 30, 1977 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 30, 1977 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 31, 1978 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 31, 1978 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 32, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 33, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 34, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 35, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 36, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 36, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 37, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 38, 1979 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 38, 1979 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 39, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 40, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 41, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 42, 1980 (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 42, 1980 (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 43, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 44, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 45, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 46, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 47, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 48, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 49, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 50, 1981 (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 50, 1981 (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Chronicle of Lithuanian Catholic Church, no. 51, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Dievas ir Trevyne, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Lietuvos Ateitis, no. 7, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Pastoge, no. 1, 1978, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Perspektyvos, no. 9, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Tiesos Kelias, no. 1, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Varpas, no. 4, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Varpas, no. 7, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Varpas, no. 8, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Samizdat Publications. Vytus, no. 5, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Statistics. General, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Ecumenical Relations with Other Denominations. General, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Roman Catholic Church in Lithuania. Children and Youth, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 24)